A Guide to the Office of the President, Special Assistants and Assistants to the Presidents, Office Administrative Files, 1981-1982
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Office of the President, Special Assistants and Assistants to the Presidents, Office Administrative Files 1981-1982
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-2/6/1.911
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1991 April 11.
Contents List
- George Bush Visit - Ed[ucational] Summit 1989 Sep (Box 1)
- George Bush Visit - Finances 1989 Sep (Box 1)
- George Bush Visit - Gifts 1989 Aug (Box 1)
- George Bush Visit - Meals (Food) 1989 Sep (Box 1)
- George Bush Visit - New Governor's Activity (NGA) 1988 (Box 1)
- George Bush Visit - Organization 1989 Sep (Box 1)
- George Bush Visit - Photos 1989 (Box 1)
- George Bush Visit - Physical Plant 1989 Sep (Box 1)
- George Bush Visit - Press 1989 Aug (Box 1)
- Public Sessions 1989 Sep (Box 1)
- George Bush Visit - Schedule - Ed[ucation] Summit 1989 Sep (Box 1)
- George Bush Visit - Security 1989 Sep (Box 1)
- George Bush Visit - Speech 1988 Dec (Box 1)
- George Bush Visit - Speeches 1989 Sep (Box 1)
- George Bush Visit - Tickets 1988 (Box 1)
- George Bush Visit - Tickets 1989 Sep (Box 1)
- George Bush Visit - Volunteers 1989 (Box 1)
- Chaban - Delmas Visit 1986 Aug (Box 2)
- Fraternity/Sorority Facilities Committee - Correspondence (1 of 4) 1982 (Box 2)
- Fraternity/Sorority Facilities Committee - Correspondence (2 of 4) 1982 (Box 2)
- Fraternity/Sorority Facilities Committee - Correspondence (3 of 4) 1982 (Box 2)
- Fraternity/Sorority Facilities Committee - Correspondence (4 of 4) 1989 (Box 2)
- French Delegate Visit 1989 Apr (Box 2)
- Thesis 1981 Jul (Box 2)